# ANTHONY MARRONE

graphic designer, photographer, layout designei

66

Highly creative and imaginative student with vast knowledge of the Adobe Creative Cloud as well as other mediums. Extensive experience with working within a team as well as managing them. Versatile skill-set with an eagerness to learn more.



(248) 231-0515



am919117@ohio.edu

## **Education:**

William Mason High School Aug 2014 - May 2018

Obtained high school diploma from William Mason High School.

Ohio University Aug 2018 - May 2022

Majoring in Visual Communication: Multimedia at the SCRIPPS School of Communication with a minor in Marketing.

# **Experience:**

University Program Council Graphic Design Chair April 2019 - May 2020

- Designed advertisements for all events University Program Council (UPC) put on.
- Served on the Executive Board to produce the best experiences for the students of Ohio University.

#### Phi Gamma Delta, Alpha Omega Historian Dec 2019 - Dec 2020

- Served on the Chapter's Executive Cabinet, working hand-in-hand with the President to ensure all members exemplify the values of the fraternity.
- Oversaw New Member Education, Brotherhood, Intramural Sports and Recruitment Chairmen.
- · Authority on all aspects of the fraternity ritual.

#### Fraternity Social Media Committee Member Dec 2020 - Present

- Designed graphics needed for the fraternity's social media as well as print media.
- Served on the fraternity's social media committee to help manage and coordinate all of our social media.

#### Sales Associate at Home Depot June 2019 - Present

- · Maintain knowledge of various products.
- Determine customers needs and present solutions.

#### The Post Layout Designer Aug 2018 - Dec. 2018

- Designed creatively formatted page layouts for the Ohio University newspaper, "The Post".
- Collaborated with a team of photographers, writers, and other layout designers to format the whole newspaper.

### Design Studio Internship Aug 2017 - June 2018

• Designed graphics, artwork and promotional items for clients brought in by the studio.

## Technical Skills:

Adobe InDesign
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Bridge
Adobe Premiere Pro
Adobe After Effects
Powerpoint
Photography
HTML
CSS
JavaScript

#### Social Skills:

Cooperative People Person Team Player Creativity